// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "This yellow-white, spectral F-type star is located in the constellation Carina south of the ecliptic. It ranks second in apparent brightness among the stars :",
    answer: "Canopus",
    options: [
      "Canopus",
      "Alpha Centauri",
      "Castor",
      "Rigel"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "When two heavenly bodies occupy the same longitude, the bodies are said to be in :",
    answer: "conjunction",
    options: [
      "sympathy",
      "conjunction",
      "parallel",
      "series"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The study of the origin and evolution of the universe is known as :",
    answer: "cosmology",
    options: [
      "tomography",
      "cystoscopy",
      "cryology",
      "cosmology"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What percentage of the Sun's mass has been converted to energy ?",
    answer: ".001%",
    options: [
      "50%",
      "1%",
      "2%",
      ".001%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "According to Kepler's Laws, all orbits of the planets are :",
    answer: "ellipses",
    options: [
      "ellipses",
      "parabolas",
      "hyperbolas",
      "square"
    ]
  },
  
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "According to Kepler's Laws, the cube of the mean distance of a planet from the sun is proportional to the :",
     answer: "square of the period",
    options: [
       "area that is swept out",
       "cube of the period",
       "square of the period",
       "fourth power of the mean distance"
     ]
   },
   
   {
      numb: 7,
     question: "What type of visible star is the coolest ?",
     answer: "M",
    options: [
       "O",
       "A",
       "G",
       "M"
     ]
   },
   { numb: 8,
     question: "Which type of star is maintained by the pressure of an electron gas ?",
     answer: "White Dwarf",
    options: [
       "Main Sequence Star",
       "White Dwarf",
       "Neutron Star",
       "Black Hole"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 9,
     question: "In our solar system, which planet has a moon with a mass closest to its own ?",
     answer: "Pluto",
    options: [
       "Earth",
       "Mars",
       "Jupiter",
       "Pluto"
     ]
   },
   {
   numb: 10,
     question: "Io, Europa, Ganymede and Callisto are satellites of what planet ?",
     answer: "Jupiter",
    options: [
       "Jupiter",
       "Saturn",
       "Neptune",
       "Uranus"
     ]
   },
];